(The middle of the day with the summer heat still lingering)
We're in Gwanyang-dong? So we're in Anyang today.
(Today's spare time, Anyang)
(Jae Seok is all alone.)
Where's Yeon Seok?
(Sneaking into the cafe)
(Chuckling)
What's he doing?
Come on.
(Surprise!)
- The cake... This is frustrating.
- Happy birthday to you
This is frustrating. I mean, I'm grateful.
(The episode was filmed on August 14, Jae Seok's birthday.)
(Happy birthday to you)
- Happy birthday, dear Jae Seok - All right.
- Happy birthday to you - Thank you.
All right.
I mean, this birthday cake...
- It's too big.
- It's for you.
- It was custom-made for you.
- I won't take this home.
- Why not?
- Why? This cake looks great.
- No.
If I take this home... This is too big for my family.
We should cut the cake here.
How can we cut this here?
- We have to.
- How can we do that here?
- My gosh.
- How...
Let's use a knife and cut it up.
I ought to celebrate my birthday with everyone.
- My goodness.
- How...
I'm just going to cut it.
(Ruthless)
- You just have to cut it like this.
- Jae Seok. But...
(Slicing it as if he's slicing tofu)
- So...
- Your hand...
What?
- You just cut your hand.
- That doesn't matter.
Why?
I'll be honest. This isn't my kind of birthday celebration.
- I'm sure you know that.
- But the cake...
- Let me take a photo of you.
- Gosh, no.
Why would I take a photo of myself?
(Suddenly taking a picture of a cut-up cake)
- Why... Give that to me.
- I'm good.
- Let me take it for you.
No, I don't want a photo.
- Let me take it with my phone.
- Hey.
Anyway, thank you.
Thank you for thinking of me.
- Over there. It says, "coffee."
- This place...
(Striding toward)
(Their handsome facial features...)
(chase away the summer heat.)
(Today's Whenever Friends: Hyun Bin and Woo Do Hwan)
(Since when were you this beautiful, Ms. Gil Ra Im?)
(He starred in every successful romantic drama.)
(That's dangerous.)
What's dangerous?
(Your romantic gaze as you worry about me.)
(With just a gaze, he can make our hearts flutter,)
(send chills down our spine,)
(or look sorrowful...)
(and scary.)
(He dominates the scenes with his gaze...)
(and seals the deal with his action scenes.)
(An all-time legend)
(Actor Hyun Bin)
(Exuding rugged charisma with his whole body)
(He taught them a lesson with his fists.)
I like you.
(A gentle, romantic charm)
(An all-rounder of genres who can balance charisma and romance)
(Actor Woo Do Hwan)
Are they filming now?
(Peeking through)
(Hovering around the cafe instead of going in)
What are they doing?
(Peeking in again)
Let's go in.
(Hiding again)
- Should I pretend I'm alone?
- Yes.
(Secretly playing hard-to-get)
- Do Hwan.
- My gosh. Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Who's that over there? Isn't that Hyun Bin?
- Someone's hiding there.
- It's him, isn't it?
- No.
- Yes.
- It's him.
- I see.
Hello.
(Hyun Bin is here.)
(Hyun Bin's first variety show)
Hey, Hyun Bin.
Hello.
Hey, look at you. You got more muscular.
(They work out at the same gym.)
Look at his chest.
(The two Whenever Friends with an unusual aura)
- Let's sit down.
- Please sit down.
- It's Jae Seok's birthday.
- Right.
- Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday to you
(Singing right away)
They already sang the song.
(Laughing)
- My gosh. The look on his face.
- Okay.
There was no emotion whatsoever.
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
They already sang the song.
- You've bulked up even more.
- Really?
- I can't feel the difference.
- Seriously.
- Right?
- He bulked up a lot.
- Both of them have a great body.
- My gosh, no.
You actually look slim next to him.
- Right. I look...
- You know?
Both of you look... Wait, you...
I'm a fish bone today.
(He looks especially slim today.)
Hyun Bin, you don't seem to age at all.
- You look the same too.
- Gosh, no. I look pretty old now.
- Happy birthday to you - I got older just today.
(Happy birthday to you)
- He's teasing me.
- Is this how it will be today?
Hyun Bin is teasing me about my age.
He's teasing me.
(He can't hide his playful side.)
Hold on. You've never met Hyun Bin?
- Well, we...
- We've never worked together.
But we met at movie premieres and other events.
- Right. Like awards ceremonies.
- We said hello then.
- But you never worked together.
- Right.
- I've heard so much about you.
- That's right.
Se Jong and Director Kim told me so much about you.
- I always wanted to meet you.
- Right.
- I feel close to him on the inside.
- Yes.
- I like him.
Well, he and I used to go to the same gym.
But now, he's working out at another gym.
The gym?
The director at the gym will be sad.
I'll stop there.
We used to work out at the same gym.
We used to sweat it out together.
- Right.
- He came over...
and spotted me on my tricep workout.
- He spotted you? Right?
- Yes, he did.
Hyun Bin spotted me on my workout.
I think he's gotten slimmer than the last time I saw him.
- Because he moved.
- Right, he's at another gym now.
- You have no one to spot you.
- I bet no one spots you.
He used to spot me.
(Turning into a fish bone due to his absence)
Gong Yoo and Hyun Bin used to be the top two members.
He's working out at another gym for now.
You guys starred in "Made in Korea."
- That's Season 2, right?
- It's Season 2.
("Made in Korea 2")
- Right.
- Tell us about the plot.
- There.
- So...
(Suddenly putting Do Hwan on the spot)
- Well...
- There.
He didn't even think about it.
(Handing over the chance to describe the drama right away)
I've been making him answer a lot of questions.
- Is that so? I see.
- Yes.
Season 2 picks up 9 years after Season 1.
So there's a 9-year jump between Seasons 1 and 2.
("'Made in Korea,' the Most-Watched Korean Title in the World")
(Baek Gi Tae of KCIA pursues wealth and power.)
(A persistent prosecutor, Jang Gon Yeong, chases him.)
(An elite officer, Baek Gi Hyeon,)
(tries to step out of his brother's shadow.)
(And 9 years later)
I've been waiting for this moment for a very long time.
(Baek Gi Tae is charging ahead in pursuit of greater power.)
(And his brother is dreaming of becoming the new power.)
(Their war for ultimate power grows fiercer.)
("Made in Korea 2")
- Yes.
- Really?
That's amazing.
Well, the drama is...
- based on a true story.
- Yes.
That was so interesting.
It's not based on a true story.
(Seal those lips.)
(Startled)
- It's not?
- It's not based on a true story.
- Really? It's not?
- Hey.
The plane was hijacked.
- Oh, those events in the drama?
- The plane was hijacked.
- It was only for that episode.
- I see. Right.
- Based on an actual incident.
- When it started.
- Yes.
- It was based on the incident.
- It was used only as a reference.
- I see.
- That's right.
- Yes.
(I'm sorry.)
You apologize fast.
- I thought he meant...
- Right. So...
- the whole drama.
- I see.
- Okay.
- You can check it out...
on September 9 on the streaming website.
- September 9.
- Please check out our drama.
We're in Anyang right now.
Which one of you has ties to Anyang?
Who is it? Is it you, Hyun Bin? No?
I was born and raised here.
I see. This is your hometown.
- Yes. Right.
- Oh, I remember.
- But you live in Seoul now?
- Yes.
When did you leave Anyang?
I was in my early 20s back then.
- I stayed here until my early 20s.
- I see.
I actually met his father before coming here today.
- My father...
- Really?
- He works...
- right across the street.
- He works nearby.
He dropped by briefly earlier before going to work.
He wanted to see his son.
- He dropped by?
- Yes, he dropped by briefly.
- I see.
- This is when he goes to work.
- And he went to work?
- Yes.
That makes you young.
You must be young if your father still goes to work.
(A unique metric for youth)
- My father is retired.
- Our fathers are all retired.
- Right. That didn't cross my mind.
- It's true, isn't it?
If both of his parents are still working...
- What about your friends?
- They still live here.
Some of them are still here.
They were born and raised here. And they're raising kids...
in Anyang.
- Right. They got married.
- And...
they still live in the same building they grew up in.
They got the adjacent unit.
I see that often with my friends.
Great. Let's start our episode with Hyun Bin and Do Hwan.
Then you have to develop new games every week?
- Yes.
- Right.
They have Game Development HQ.
- Do you play games there?
- Yes.
- They play the games themselves.
- Every week.
They create new games too.
- You're both athletic.
- Right.
I guess we can look forward to good results today.
Okay. Once you try it out...
Are you good at games?
Games?
- I've never seen him play games.
- It depends on the game.
Games like Alkkagi where you have to flick your finger.
I don't think I'll be bad at it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Aren't you good with ball games?
- I'm good with ball games.
- Yes.
(Surprised)
(Screaming)
(Shouting)
(Impossible to conceal his engagement in the games)
(You can see Hyun Bin...)
(fully engrossed in the games pretty soon.)
Great. Let's start our episode in Anyang.
- In Anyang.
- Yes.
- Her name is "Hwang Ye Rin."
- Ye Rin.
"Little Lee Dae Hoons..."
"and Little Cho Seong Jins are training here."
"We start our day off with an enthusiastic meeting."
"We spend every waking moment together from dawn to dusk."
"We're alike in both appearance and passion."
"Come and watch two peas in a pod bring the chemistry."
I guess they're in the music industry.
- Right?
- Two peas in a pod?
They spend every waking moment together.
What? They must be married then.
It's 15 minutes away on foot.
- Really? Let's get going.
- Yes.
- It's pretty hot.
- Gosh, it's hot.
This is...
But it's gotten cooler.
- Right.
- Yes.
- It's gotten cooler, right?
- Compared to before.
It's much better now.
But it is still hot.
- Right?
- Come to the shade.
- Come here.
- It's hot.
- Come to the shade.
- Okay.
My gosh. Last week...
- Come here.
Actually...
He naturally ended up...
- in the sun again.
- For five days...
- Come to the shade.
- Hey.
You guys told me to come to the shade.
Were you able to go away for the summer?
- Go away?
- For the summer.
- Go away for the summer.
It's been a while anyone asked me that.
Or a summer break?
We went on a trip for our son.
We're trying to spend time together.
- Right.
- Yes.
That's natural.
I didn't get to go on a trip with my family this summer.
Last year, we went on a short domestic trip...
for a couple of days.
- Yes.
- But not this year.
Do you even have time for that?
- That's why we couldn't go.
- Right?
This year has been so busy.
It's been a while since I walked outside like this.
- If you think about it, - Yes.
you don't walk around like this...
- once you grow up.
- That's true.
This used to be one of my regular alleys growing up.
- This alley?
- I see.
There is some kind of stream here.
Right.
(They keep on walking.)
I doubt they could film it.
(Screaming)
(Waving)
- They're so happy.
- Gosh.
- The locals are very welcoming.
- Yes.
Anyang is welcoming me.
Didn't they wave at Hyun Bin?
- I think so.
- That's why I blocked him.
(Guarding Hyun Bin)
I had a feeling that they'd do that, so I blocked him.
- What?
- Hi.
We have to cross on the left.
Yeon Seok!
Hello.
Yeon Seok! Class 634!
- What's going on?
- He's my junior from the Air Force.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
- Hey.
- He brought up the Air Force again.
- Hold on.
- Why?
- He brings that up every week.
- Every week?
- He was my junior driver.
- Really?
- My gosh.
- Seriously. Yeon Seok...
- That's crazy.
always mentions Sejong University...
and the Air Force.
I thought he wouldn't mention them today.
I can't believe you ran into your junior from the Air Force.
I ran into him in Anyang, of all places.
- What a small world.
- Here...
- It's been so long.
- I can't believe it happened here.
Right. My gosh.
(I love the Air Force.)
- It's better in the shade.
- Yes.
(They enter a shaded street.)
(Staring)
Wait. Look over there. That's my high school.
- What? Where?
- I graduated from there.
(They spot Do Hwan's alma mater.)
- That one? Pyeongchon.
- Pyeongchon Management High School.
- I see. That's your alma mater?
- We have to go that way.
Yes. That's my alma mater.
They changed the name.
- Why?
- It used to be called...
Information High School.
I remember that.
They told me it'd be easier to get into college.
- Right.
- Yes.
Are you good with computers?
Not really.
I was in Internet Information Department.
I had to study and get the certificates.
But to do that, I had to go to school on weekends.
- I had to take the exam. Yes.
- To get the certificates?
So I just gave up.
- I...
- Because you had to go on weekends?
Right. I had to play soccer on weekends.
- You like playing soccer.
- Yes.
I could put up with the week because I had soccer.
- To play soccer on weekends.
- For soccer.
(A boy who loved playing soccer)
(Do Hwan has returned!)
I used to do the push-up position a lot over there.
- Where?
- In front of the gate.
- In front of the gate?
- Let me explain.
- When you're late...
- For being late? I see.
- I bet you did the squat walk too.
- So many students had to do it too.
- Right.
- Yes.
(Staring)
I used to take that path to go to school when I was young.
My house was that way back then.
I wanted to have ripped abs, growing up.
I always walked this path while hitting my abs.
- To get defined abs?
- I was just reminded of that...
- after seeing that path.
- I see.
- This is what you did?
- Yes.
I've never done sit-ups.
I sculpted my abs by hitting them.
(The abs sculpted through punches)
- Are you for real?
- He's an odd one.
You used your hands...
- instead of the machine.
- Yes, that's it.
- There's a belt for that.
- Right.
Someone told me about this method when I was growing up.
- So you punched your abs like this?
- That's right.
I used to punch them. If they hurt, I used my fingers.
- Gosh, you're something else too.
- I didn't know about this.
That's crazy.
We're almost there.
- Hold on.
- Where is it? Is this the place?
(They stop at...)
- Hold on.
- "Taekwondo?"
"Taekwondo?"
(A taekwondo studio?)
- This is the place.
- Isn't it a piano academy?
- This is it. Piano.
- It's on the second floor.
- "Piano."
- "Music."
- Taekwondo.
- It was about music.
Taekwondo and music.
- Taekwondo and music.
- That's right.
She mentioned Lee Dae Hoon.
- Right.
- I guess they run both places.
- They must run both places.
- That's interesting.
I see.
That's the taekwondo studio, and this is the piano academy.
There she is.
- Are you Ye Rin?
- Yes.
- Hello. You're Ye Rin?
- I'm Hwang Ye Rin.
- Nice to meet you.
- Okay.
- Can we come inside?
- You can go that way.
- To the studio?
- Yes.
It's nice and cool here. Gosh.
- Hello.
- This way.
- You guys are a family.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Right?
- Yes.
Your daughter wrote to our show.
That's right.
- Nice to meet you. Hello.
- Hello.
It's clear that you guys are a family. Aren't you?
- Yes, we are.
- You guys have the same eyes.
- Seriously.
- Wait.
- The three of you...
- They resemble each other a lot.
have the same eyes.
- Your eyes and mouth...
- Copy and paste.
- So you must be the music teacher.
- Yes.
- And you teach taekwondo.
- Right.
How long have you been running this taekwondo studio?
I've been running the studio in Pyeongchon for 11 years.
And I ran a taekwondo studio in Geumcheon-gu, Seoul...
- for 17 years.
- I see.
What about the piano academy?
It's the same as his answer.
- Oh, exactly the same?
- Yes.
- So both places...
- We've been...
- have always been together?
- Yes.
(From 1999 until now,)
(the father's shout and the mother's melody...)
(have been together for 28 years.)
(The two businesses have been like a packaged deal.)
How did you and your brother end up doing taekwondo?
I was born as the daughter of a taekwondo director.
So I took up taekwondo as a little girl.
Now, I'm working under him...
- as a taekwondo instructor.
- You're a taekwondo instructor.
So you began practicing taekwondo...
when you were a little girl.
But was there a reason that made you decide...
to work with your parents?
Actually, I got into college as an English literature major.
- English literature?
- Yes. But...
my father suffered from a stroke and collapsed when I was 20.
Then COVID-19 broke out.
He couldn't find any instructors.
I thought my family was in trouble...
and I should help them.
So I started helping out around the studio.
Then I began working as an instructor.
So I've been here for seven years.
I see. Your father had a health problem.
But this is great. You're fully recovered from it.
We bonded more deeply as a family...
after I got sick.
So we're a strong, united family now.
I'm very happy now.
You have nothing to worry about with your children here.
It's wonderful to see how they're holding the line...
at the studio to keep the establishment going.
- He must feel so reassured.
- Yes.
Please tell us what made you write to our show.
When we wake up, we have a meal together.
Then we take the same car to come to work.
Then we work together.
We also go home together.
We follow the same routine every day.
And we talk about the same things.
I was looking for a way to make our day special.
That's why I wrote to your show.
- Is life boring these days?
- Yes.
Yes.
(A very firm answer)
- It's understandable.
- Yes.
Think about it. She's so young.
- She's always... right.
- She's always around little kids.
- Yes.
- You know? She must be bored.
- We'll give you a dopamine rush.
- Let's do this. Gosh.
- Thank you.
- He's the Son of Anyang.
All right. Let's play the games now.
Okay. Let's begin with Round One.
"Whether we're commuting or heading out on weekend outings,"
"the whole family rides together."
"A 300-dollar gas gift card."
(Round 1 present: 300-dollar gas gift card)
A gas gift card.
- All right. A gas gift card.
- That's 300 dollars.
(A present for the family who's on the road a lot)
(Taekwon: Break the Cans)
(Use the taekwondo mitt to hit a ball...)
(and knock down the cans.)
(Round 1)
(6 target cans)
(They're given 10 balls...)
(and 30 seconds to finish.)
- With the mitt?
- Hit the ball with the mitt.
Knock down the cans?
I hope we succeed today.
Wait. How can we do it with this mitt?
With the mitt?
(6 cans, the starting line)
- This is hard.
- It's so hard.
- Let's practice.
- Go ahead.
Go ahead, Bin.
(Hyun Bin practices first.)
(Leaning toward right)
- I see. It's going that way.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- This is hard.
- This is...
- It's so hard.
I should aim it low.
Not that.
(The balls keep flying toward right.)
I should...
(Taking a step forward)
(Flying off)
It looks like you're not good at this.
- Hyun Bin. What's going on?
- Gosh.
Because I can't hit the cans, this feels...
- I see. This is...
- Do Hwan.
- This is hard. It's not easy.
- It's so hard.
- Wait.
- I see.
(He hits the bottom can, and the cans tumble down.)
Just like that.
- That's how you do it.
- If we hit the bottom ones,
- The bottom ones... Yes.
- the other cans will fall off.
- We need to aim it well.
- It has to be spot on.
It's hard to zero in on it.
- Wait. So...
- Try it.
to finish it off...
You got it.
Okay.
(Yeon Seok perfects the push-and-hit method.)
- Wait. It has to be accurate.
- Yes. That's great.
It has to be accurate toward the end.
- Yes.
- I see.
It's going to be tough when there's only one left.
(Hitting the box)
I think I sort of got the angle. You know what?
Finishing the last one...
- That's hard.
- It's hard.
Should I do it this way?
(Do Hwan who got the hang of it tries next.)
You got it.
(Surprised)
He's indeed from Anyang.
I'm from Anyang.
That's great.
(Hyun Bin feels anxious as Do Hwan nails it.)
- Go.
- Practice.
My gosh.
- I think this might work.
- It's not that accurate.
(Bullseye)
- You got the hang of it now.
- Yes, that's better.
- Do whatever suits your style.
- Right?
(Another bullseye)
- Great.
- Hey, this is great.
- This method is working.
Then why don't you go first and do a smash shot?
Break the tower first.
- Let's do this.
- You should go either 1st or 2nd.
Let's split the balls 3, 3, 2, and 2.
- The numbers? We'll throw two.
- Yes.
- Three, three, two, and two.
- The order...
- Why don't you go 1st?
- Yes, you should go 1st.
- Do Hwan, you're second.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Let's do a group cheer.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- All right. One.
- Bring it in.
- In 1, 2, 3. Here we go!
- Yes!
- Let's go.
- Do Hwan. Come here.
- Okay.
Let us know before you begin.
Here we go.
- All right.
- Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
Set...
(Loading up his pocket with the balls)
(1st try)
- Go.
- You have two left.
- Yes!
- What's that?
- This is bad.
That's really bad.
- That's the worst.
- That can...
That's really bad.
- That's the worst.
- This is bad.
That's the worst. We're in trouble.
- Hold on.
- No. Hit it hard.
- Hit it hard.
- Hit it hard? What should I do?
- Gosh.
- You have one left.
- Great job. Yes!
- Oh, my!
(Clearing away the obstacle too)
Yes. That's good.
(Happy)
- Just 1, Jae Seok.
- It's the toughest 1.
- Come on.
- Oh, dear.
That's it. One left.
- Yeon Seok!
- One left!
- Go slow.
- Four, three, two...
(The last ball and last target)
Three, two...
Two...
(Yoo One Shot's clean shot)
(A thrilling success right before time ran out)
(Jumping)
Success!
(Yoo One Shot did it.)
Thank you!
- Nice one, Yeon Seok.
- Thank you.
- Round One, success!
- Success!
(Succeeded on the very first try)
In the last chance, you know?
The dopamine.
You did well.
We've been on a roll since last week.
- Gosh.
- My gosh.
- This is wild.
- What's wrong?
My heart is pounding.
- Round One.
- You feel the dopamine rush.
- That was just Round One.
- You really feel the dopamine rush.
All right, we succeeded in Round One.
Decide whether to go or stop before Round Two.
- Go!
We have plenty of tries left.
All right. Please check the second prize.
"The cleaning master that will keep..."
"the dojo spotless for disciples roaming around every inch of it."
"Roborock robot vacuum."
(Round 2 present: Roborock robot vacuum)
- Gosh, a robot vacuum?
- It's a robot vacuum.
- My gosh.
- This is...
It will be useful in the dojo...
- My gosh.
- and at home.
The wife is already...
- I get it.
- The director is already...
The vacuum cleaner could clean the piano academy...
- after it's done here.
- Exactly.
(In charge of the taekwondo studio and piano academy)
(Round 2)
(10 target cans)
- Ten?
- There's more now.
(Added 4 more cans to the bottom row of targets)
- Ten cans, exactly.
- It wouldn't be bad for Hyun Bin...
- to knock off...
- Sounds good.
the cans hard in the beginning,
- as the 1st or 2nd player.
- Okay.
Do you want to go last?
- I'll try.
- The last player.
- Do the last 3.
- I'll do 2.
- I'll only try 2.
- No, do 3.
Come on. How about a group cheer?
- Okay.
- Let's do it.
- In 1...
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
(Good luck on Round 2!)
Good luck.
- Do we leave it here?
- Yes.
Please call it.
Here I go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
Ready. Set.
(2nd try)
(4 in 1 go)
- That's it.
- Just knock them all down.
- We're done.
- It's over.
- Well done.
- Good job.
- Unbelievable.
- Amazing.
- Hyun Bin!
- Otherworldly Bin!
Unbelievable.
- Hyun Bin!
- Otherworldly Bin!
- Please.
It's okay.
Hold on. Try being accurate.
- Please.
- Do Hwan.
- It's your turn. Slowly.
- Three balls.
(2nd try)
- Try hitting it low.
- Five seconds left.
- Four, three, - One can.
- Slowly.
- two, one.
(The Son of Anyang did it.)
(Do Hwan's perfect buzzer-beater)
- What?
- Oh, my gosh!
How did it happen?
Oh, my gosh. Thank you!
Really!
- Congratulations.
(A high five)
Unbelievable.
(Cleared Round 2 in 1 go)
- Unbelievable.
- For real.
- It was like a drama scene.
- That was...
Round Two,
- success!
- Success!
The accuracy, you know?
- Gosh, that was tough.
- Well done.
- In the beginning...
- Hyun Bin got us on a good start,
and Do Hwan wrapped it up well.
(Hyun Bin's good start and Do Hwan's good finish)
All right, the last round,
- Round Three.
- Yes.
Go or stop. In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
- I trust Hyun Bin.
- It's go big or go home for us.
I love you, Hyun Bin.
She suddenly said, "I love you, Hyun Bin."
The director must be a fan.
"The whole family has more than dozens of uniforms."
True, and it's really tough.
"An LG Styler to get rid of all the sweat smell."
(Round 3 present: LG Styler)
(The appliance that keeps your clothes looking their best)
- It's from LG!
- How generous of the team.
- Amazing. It's...
- Right?
- This is really.
- Here, I'll take it.
- Hold on. We haven't won it yet.
- What?
- We haven't won the Styler yet.
- Okay, thank you.
- You see...
- She's already taking a photo.
(Suddenly feeling the pressure)
- What matters is from now on.
- She's adorable.
- You see...
- The difficulty shoots up...
- in Round Three.
- We've got a jinx.
After succeeding in...
- Rounds 1 and 2 in a flash, - Right.
- we struggle really badly...
- You take long, right?
and fail many times...
- in Round Three.
- Yes, we failed numerous times.
- Today...
- Right.
- You can do it.
- Round Three.
- We've got the chance left.
- Right.
- You can use it.
- What's for Round Three?
(Round 3)
(The ball gets small.)
(The ball for Rounds 1 and 2)
(The ball for Round 3)
Do the cans get small?
- It's the ball.
- Is it the ball that gets small?
The ball would have less impact.
It's best to hit it hard.
This is...
I might need to hit harder.
You should hit it hard.
It's best to hit the ball hard.
They won't fall over.
- It's...
- What?
This is bad.
(Still standing after a direct hit)
- It's...
- What?
- This is bad.
- Going for Round Three...
might've been a bad idea.
Hitting the cans doesn't do anything.
We've got to hit the ball really hard.
- The bottom row...
- This won't work for me.
This is really bad.
So I need to hit it really hard.
(Thinking)
The cans won't budge when hit at the bottom.
It's best to hit from above.
A smash.
(Slightly moving)
Come on.
- I pushed them in.
- Well done.
- You...
(Two thumbs up)
- Why don't we...
- The bottom.
change the order?
- Do Hwan...
- Should I start us off?
- No.
- No?
- You were weak.
- Come on.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Do Hwan should hit first.
- We'll go 2nd and 3rd.
- Yes, 2nd and 3rd.
No, don't.
Stop!
(A battle of offense and defense)
No, don't.
The clash between them is intense.
It's intense.
- Let's cheer for Round Three.
- Come.
- Go.
- With all the strength,
- whenever possible, go!
- Go!
- Starting with Do Hwan.
- Do I go first?
Okay.
- Call it.
- Here I go.
We still have many tries left.
- Ready. Set.
- Relax, okay?
(Anxious)
- Don't cross the line.
- Got it.
- Ready. Set.
- Here I go.
(3rd try)
Nice.
(He hit the bottom row.)
(Do Hwan knocked down 4 alone.)
The position was great.
It feels like we're in Round One.
Oh, no.
(3rd try)
- Jae Seok.
- This is bad.
- No, it's okay. We're still safe.
- It's okay. He'll make it.
- That's it. Nice.
- Good job.
- You did it! We'll make it!
- Hyun Bin!
We'll make it!
(They hit it three times in a row.)
No way.
- Four, three...
- Hit at least one.
One.
(Failed)
That was so close.
- We were on a roll.
- What a bummer.
- It's tough.
- How many tries do we have?
- They have seven tries left.
- Seven?
- It's tough when there's one left.
- That was tough.
You've got to aim at it.
Hyun Bin hit four in total.
Yes, of course.
- You blew the whistle.
- He knew, okay?
- You blew it, so I tried.
- He knew.
But Hyun Bin also got a little frustrated.
Gosh, hold on.
Going last is nerve-racking.
- Should I go down on our knees?
- Good luck!
- I'll do it.
- No, I'll do it.
All set.
Can you move them to the edge?
No one is backing down.
- The war of nerves between the two.
- Right?
Let's do a group cheer. Come.
- Round 3.
- In 1, 2, 3. Go!
- Here we go.
- Three balls each.
- Fourth try. Ready.
- Should I try it low like this?
- Set.
- Maybe about this far?
- You've got to crush them.
- Crush them? Got it.
The first players should crush them.
Ready. Set.
(4th try)
- Well done!
- My gosh.
Nice. Okay.
(4th try)
(He hit the very center.)
(Surprised)
- Three more cans.
- I might make it.
- Good.
- We did our part.
- Two more left. We're all set.
- Now...
- We're all set.
Hwan.
- Calm down.
- The accuracy matters now.
- Do Hwan.
- Yes?
- Take it slow.
I can't hit it like this.
- Hold on.
- I can't hit it like this.
(4th try)
- Five, four, three...
- Hold on.
(4th try)
- Come on.
- One can.
It's that one can.
(Groaning)
It's okay.
If only I had done better.
(He hit 0 cans.)
It's okay.
(The 1 agonizing can)
Practice. It's okay.
That was so close.
- I should've done my part.
- It was really close.
Should I just hit it like this? I'm really losing it.
What's the secret behind it? Why can't I do it?
We shouldn't think that...
we have plenty of chances left.
- No.
- The difficulty shot up...
in Round Three.
- Right away?
- Right away.
The order...
(Walking)
- The order... Do Hwan.
- I'll go first.
- Go first, Do Hwan.
- Do Hwan.
Do Hwan lacks a little in accuracy.
Why is he always there?
(Delicate hand movements)
- Why is Do Hwan always there?
- Don't focus on that too much.
- But it helps.
- Right.
(Praiseworthy)
(The production crew realigns the cans.)
Tries 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10. So 5 tries.
The number of Do Hwan's shots...
- Take one out?
- Yes.
(A cutthroat performance-based system)
Let's take out...
- one of Do Hwan's shots.
- Or I'll hit two.
No, it's better...
to have someone good hit four times.
The chances are better if you hit them consecutively.
(Someone good has appeared.)
(Cleared 4 cans)
From what I see, at a close distance...
You have to hit hard.
- Okay, got it.
- Good.
You nail it in practice,
but when it's the real deal, especially as the last player...
- Yes, going last...
- It makes you nervous, right?
I get seriously nervous.
His countdown from five makes me nervous.
Totally. When he goes, "Five, four, three, two, one."
The moment I hear "five,"
it feels like things go faster than I expect.
(The 5-second pressure even gets to Hyun Bin.)
Why am I shaking?
- Do Hwan, you must be in a slump.
- He's a little...
- What if it gets worse?
- It's okay.
Practice more, Do Hwan.
(Trying to overcome it by practicing)
Good luck!
Do Hwan was good until now.
(Do Hwan was the ace at the start.)
- Aim at it.
- Hit it hard.
How about this?
- I can cross it after, right?
- Yes.
- It's after I hit it.
- It's after he hit the ball.
(A spectacular breakfall)
Nice one.
- That was good, right?
- Nice.
Nice one.
That's the one.
- Good.
- Hit one ball, just like that.
- Got it.
- One.
- Hit one ball like that.
- One ball, just like that.
- Okay.
Good. Do Hwan, I've got a good feeling about this.
Let's give it a shot.
- Let's go!
- Good luck!
(1 ball, 1 ball, 4 balls, 4 balls)
- Here I go.
- Okay.
Ready. Sixth try. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
- Sixth try.
- Please.
Set.
Crush them.
(6th try)
One more.
- No, I only got 1 ball.
- He only got 1 ball.
- Why only 1?
- He got 1.
(They forgot about the strategy already.)
(At least I hit it!)
- Go for it!
- We agreed on one.
- What?
- That was so close.
- You got one ball, Jae Seok.
- Is that so?
- Did I only get 1?
- Yes, 1 ball.
You only got one, Do Hwan?
- Yes. Oh, my.
- Oh, dear.
Yes, one ball.
(Yeon Seok's turn with 4 balls)
Those two are...
(6th try)
(Passed through the gap)
- The ball passed through the gap.
- What's this?
- Just one more.
- All right. One left.
- Next.
- One left.
- Now then.
- Please.
One left.
(There's 1 can left.)
- Please.
- Five, four, three,
- One left.
- two,
one.
- Oh, no.
- Goodness.
(They failed due to time running out.)
It's the time!
That was really close.
- We've got to overcome this.
- The chance...
The time!
(They failed with just 1 can left again.)
The first player should hurry.
Oh, dear.
The same player should hit it, right?
The one can that's left...
- It's tough.
- The accuracy...
Finishing that one last can is challenging.
(The last can requires precise aim.)
We'll use the chance.
- Go ahead.
- The chance.
- Should we?
- We should.
(Chance)
I hope you pick a good one.
(Among the Lucky Chances, there's 1 Unlucky Chance.)
- Pick one wisely.
- I hope it turns things around.
It'd be great if the ball changes.
- Or maybe another try.
- Yes.
- Are those the chances?
- All right.
- What does it say?
- Is it the ball?
It says one ball gets big.
- What?
- Nice one.
One ball gets big?
One?
- The 1st player.
- The 1st player should use it.
The first player.
(Highly satisfied with the chance)
- One?
- The first player...
should knock the cans down hard.
(Round 3 ball, Chance ball)
- Use it last.
- Last.
Let's use that last.
- Use it last.
- Go last, Hyun Bin.
Please go last with it.
Hyun Bin, practice with it.
- Just once?
- Imagine going at it in one go.
Practice like this.
Practice with one can.
- Oh, dear.
- Get a grip on it.
- It's...
- Okay.
- This is...
- It's scary.
It'll fly far even if you hit it lightly.
- Hit it like this.
- Hit lightly,
- and it still flies far.
- Aim for accuracy.
- This is nice.
- Yes.
- That just now.
- Try it, Jae Seok.
- No.
- That was nice just now.
- The last player should use it.
- Yes, the final shot.
The last player should use that ball.
Do Hwan looks like he wants to give it a shot.
No.
Okay. Do Hwan.
Try it, Do Hwan.
- If the cans are knocked off 1st...
- What if we knock them off 1st?
How about it?
When we hit the balls hard at first,
- He could succeed.
- things looked good.
I think I can ace it.
- Go for the final shot, Do Hwan.
- Make the final shot.
- Okay, the final shot.
- Good.
- You have the final shot.
- Okay.
- Go last. Okay.
- Do Hwan goes last.
- Give it to me.
- Give Do Hwan the final shot.
- Okay.
-The final shot.
- Yes?
- It's really...
(Hesitating)
- You...
- I'll do a good job.
(Give it to me.)
It's your chance to become the Son of Anyang.
Have faith in me. I think I can do it.
Giving you this only ball is...
Should we use this ball at the beginning or at the end?
- Jae Seok, we kept failing...
- Right.
on the one last can.
- That's the tough one.
- Okay.
- For real.
- It's our chance.
- It's literally our chance.
- I've got it.
- Okay, let's cheer for Round Three.
- We have to succeed.
- It's our chance.
- It's literally our chance.
- In one...
- Do Hwan?
(Laser focused)
- In one...
- Right.
- In one, two, three.
- Two, three.
- Go!
- Let's go!
- Good luck!
Two, three, three, and one.
- Two, three, three, and one?
- Yes.
- That makes 9.
Give us one more ball.
- Two, three, four, and one.
- Four and one.
Okay.
- From what I see, we need to hurry.
- We have to be fast.
- Good luck!
- Even the time matters.
- Right?
- We're always out of time.
- The first players should go fast.
- Let's go fast.
It's so that you have the time...
- Okay.
- to make the final shot.
I'm trying to keep my inner peace.
- Two, three, four, and one.
- All set.
- Here I go, okay?
- Go ahead.
- The chance...
- Hold on.
- We have to succeed this time.
- I'll give you the ball from here.
- Okay.
- Nice.
(Ball passer Hyun Bin)
Here we go.
Ready. Seventh try.
- Set.
- Let's go.
Crush them.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 7.)
(7th try)
- Just crush them.
- Okay, crush them.
- Oh, dear.
- That was close.
(2 balls are gone.)
We're being crushed.
(Yeon Seok has 3 balls.)
- Oh, no.
- Hurry.
- Calm down.
- One.
You can do it.
No!
(Two players failed in a flash.)
Oh, no.
Nice.
(He cleared 3 cans.)
- You must finish it.
- Oh, no.
(An unexpected scenario)
- One final shot.
- Hurry.
- Don't give up.
- Five...
You can do it. Hurry.
(Trying not to laugh)
- Good luck! Don't give up!
- Five,
four...
(Failed)
- Wait a minute.
- This is bad.
Four...
(The end of the big ball)
- I'm sorry. I'm terribly sorry.
- But...
Even though it was close...
(On his knees)
It was...
I'm sorry, I...
No, it was...
The first three players couldn't...
We couldn't help in the beginning.
It's okay.
See? Round Three is...
This happens when we finish Rounds 1 and 2 quickly.
I'm sorry.
- No, it was a tough one.
- Even if we made it...
We should've hit some in the beginning.
(Gloomy)
So what now?
We've got two tries.
- Let's get it done somehow.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Cheer up!
What's our strategy?
- I'll go 1st and hit 3.
- Okay, from the start...
- I'll hit three.
- Crush them all from the start.
Do Hwan, you go second,
- and I'll go third.
- Okay.
(With Ace Hyun Bin going 1st)
Three, two, three.
- Three, two...
- Three, two, four?
- Two, two, and three.
- Three? Okay, three.
Three, two, three.
(Mission: Hyun Bin to crush them all)
- It's...
- Should we just go for it?
- Yes. It'll only tire us out.
- True.
Let's save our energy.
- Let's go!
- Good luck!
- Ninth try.
- Let's break this jinx.
- Call it.
- Here I go.
- Ready. Set.
- Please.
- Crush them, Hyun Bin.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
(9th try)
(He failed to crush the cans.)
- One more.
- Why won't it work?
Crush them.
Crush them!
Why are you crushing those?
(Crushing the innocent balls)
Why are you crushing the balls?
(Picking up balls while playing the game)
(9th try)
(Cleared 8 cans amid the chaos)
- What?
- Three balls.
Please.
(Only 1 can left)
Four...
Five.
(Just one more!)
Four, three...
- One more!
- Slowly.
One.
(Failed)
No, hold on.
(Only 1 ball was left once again.)
It's impossible.
This is driving me crazy.
Hold on.
(Sighing)
Goodness.
This is driving me nuts.
- It's crazy.
- Hold on.
That one can.
Gosh.
Goodness.
I told him to crush them, and he crushed these.
(Why did he crush these innocent balls?)
- It's all good now, Do Hwan.
- Okay.
- He crushed the balls.
- Gosh.
Why don't the cans get crushed?
These cans are too hard.
- And they were placed too far.
- Where do they make these?
These are made in Korea.
- These are made in Korea.
- That's good. It's Korean.
You have to do better.
(The "Made in Korea" brothers need to excel at this.)
- Are those made in Korea?
- Yes, they are made in Korea.
- You can do it.
- Go!
- Let's cheer up. It's our last try.
- Let's go.
Gosh. Is this our last try?
- It's really our last try.
- My goodness.
- We'll do our best.
- Okay.
In 1, 2, 3,
- let's go!
- Let's go!
(Cheering up for the last time)
Please.
We can't fail it.
(The Son of Anyang is desperate for success.)
We have to break this jinx.
This is our last try.
Last?
It's your last try. Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
Set.
- Here I go.
- Crush them.
(Last try)
That was close.
It's amazing!
(He cleared 9 cans in 1 shot!)
This is crazy.
It's amazing. This is crazy.
- Gosh.
- Good.
Do Hwan, two balls.
Get one.
(Last try)
You have two balls.
Do Hwan.
No way. Don't tell me...
- Just one.
- Bin.
Just one more can.
You have three balls.
Just one can.
Slowly.
(Their fate depends on this last ball.)
- Just 1.
- Just 1 more.
Just one.
It was so close. Gosh.
(It's over.)
Gosh. They were so good, though.
No way.
- Gosh. Awesome.
- I'm sorry.
(Good job.)
- Do we have to take all back?
- No.
Yeon Seok was on fire this time.
- The balls are too small.
- They are.
- They had to be bigger.
- They were cruel.
(They pulled off an incredible miracle,)
I'm sorry.
(but in the end, they had to apologize.)
No.
(All presents are taken away.)
Gosh. For goodness' sake.
Gosh. I can't believe it didn't work.
(Staring)
This is too hard.
Korea is too good at manufacturing this stuff.
This can is so sturdy.
Gosh. We failed again.
(The "Made in Korea" brothers can't keep their heads up.)
It's all right.
- It's okay. Really.
- It's okay.
- We're sorry.
- It's all right.
- It's okay.
- You should get them first.
Okay. It's all right.
- What a shame.
- It suits me well.
Thank you.
(Loving it)
Okay.
(Ashamed)
I'm so mad.
We apologize.
- It's all right.
- Thank you.
We'll get going.
Thank you.
Gosh. Why didn't it work?
I've rarely felt this sorry.
I feel so bad.
- It's a bad feeling.
- Yes.
Gosh. It was close.
(Anyway, it's time for lunch.)
Anyang Big Star?
That must be it.
- The cab that's making a left turn.
- You're right.
Hello.
Gosh.
It'll only take 7 to 8 minutes.
(The mood is much gloomier than before.)
What a shame.
- It was really close.
- It was.
(He can't shake off the disappointment easily.)
- Do you feel like this every week?
- That's right.
Even if you succeeded during practice,
when the game begins,
and when the countdown begins, you can't do it.
"Five, four, three..."
That was you, Hyun Bin.
The moment I heard "five..."
- Did it make you nervous?
- Yes, it did.
- It makes you hurry.
- Yes, I felt rushed.
Gosh. We had our chances.
We had a couple of crucial chances.
- That's right.
- But we couldn't pull it off.
So, I keep thinking,
"Should we have used the big ball at first?"
Stop talking about the big ball.
No, I'm not saying it was Do Hwan's fault.
I wondered if we should've used the big ball at first.
- That's all, Do Hwan.
- What? Okay.
- I got it.
- Should we have used it at first?
If we used it, we might have pulled it off.
What a shame.
I'm getting more determined.
Gosh.
I should check what's around the place.
- Yes, that's right.
- Since we have a mouth...
Since we have a mouth, we have to eat something.
We should eat.
It's your birthday today, Jae Seok.
- Don't mind me.
- Wouldn't it be nice and cool?
Should we get some seaweed soup?
- Seaweed soup!
- That's good.
- You had it in the morning, right?
- Yes, I did.
Come on, Yeon Seok. Seriously.
You already had it in the morning.
Look how thoughtful Hyun Bin is.
Let's have what you want to have.
- No, I have nothing in mind.
- Yes.
I don't crave anything. What do you want, Do Hwan?
- You're back in your hometown.
- What about bossam and makguksu?
Sounds good, Yeon Seok.
Where is it?
There's a bossam place in this alleyway.
- They have makguksu too.
- Bossam.
They've just opened.
- Where?
- For lunch?
For lunch. It opens at 11:20am.
- They've just opened.
- That's perfect.
Gosh. Do you really go to a place without pre-arranging it?
- Yes.
- Amazing. I've never done that.
- They've just opened.
- We're right on time.
(They arrive in time for opening.)
It's nice and cool.
The aftermath of the last game lingers.
Right?
(Setting the utensils as soon as he sits down)
It was so...
- What is this?
- I mean, it went too fast.
(The youngest one is quick and efficient.)
- Okay. Let's do better.
- Yes.
I'll do my best.
Gosh. It stays with you for a long time.
- I still see it.
- You can still see it.
- You can still see the last can.
- It's a bit...
It wasn't that bad.
Hyun Bin was exhilarated before.
I was thrilled up until Round Two.
He was so excited.
(Feeling disappointed again)
Have you watched us play games at home?
- Of course.
- I see.
When you were watching,
were there any games you thought you'd succeed?
Actually,
if you had asked me this question before the last game,
I would've answered it.
Now, I can't say anything.
When this is aired on TV,
Ye Jin will probably watch it with you.
(I really have to succeed in the next mission.)
You should succeed before you leave.
That's right.
- Gosh, look at these.
- Gosh.
- They are fancy.
- Our useless mouths...
Our useless mouths will be eating.
(Garlic bossam and octopus combo)
It's well-cooked. It must be tasty.
You have to eat it with the octopus.
You make a combo out of it.
(Satisfied)
I've never had bossam with octopus.
That went really well.
He's like Jang Geum in "Jewel in the Palace."
(He's mixing makguksu.)
Please enjoy your meal comfortably.
Do Hwan's mixing the noodles with his hand right now.
He's like Jang Geum in "Jewel in the Palace."
He's good.
Where did you learn this?
(He places it neatly on a plate and serves it to the brothers.)
He's very skillful.
- Thank you.
- Were you the youngest somewhere?
He's caring for us intuitively.
He's like a good younger brother.
- Have you worked part-time before?
- Yes. Many times.
- Really?
- For what kind of jobs?
I've worked at many bakeries.
I also worked as a server at fried chicken places.
- Things like that.
- Exactly. We can tell.
Also at a pho place.
- I've done many part-time jobs.
- You look professional.
- Yes.
- Right.
- He looked like a pro.
- Yes, he did.
(Slurping the makguksu Do Hwan mixed)
Please cheer up after eating it.
Okay.
I have a lot on my mind.
We won't fail anymore.
We'll nail it in one go.
Whatever it is, we'll nail it on the first try.
Hold on.
(No more failures.)
Gosh. It was good.
By the way,
- we should play a game now.
- A game.
- Do you have your own credit cards?
- Yes.
- Did you bring yours?
We're betting on lunch.
Whose idea was it to pay with a personal card?
It just happened that way.
"It just happened."
- It just happened.
- The staff wouldn't pay.
Pouring water is fun too.
- Right.
- Without letting it overflow.
Let's use this one. It's clearer to see.
(Pouring water into the cup)
- Let's fill it up a bit.
- Do we use that bottle?
- Should we use this bottle?
- Let's pour with that bottle.
- Okay, let's do that.
- So it'll be clear and quick?
- Yes.
- I'll go first.
(Yeon Seok goes first.)
He's pushing it.
(A bold start)
(The 2nd player, Hyun Bin, is flustered.)
You went too far.
From the start?
(Hesitating)
Gosh. How do I do this?
(Standing up)
(Stopping after pouring a little)
Gosh. Look at that.
- Gosh. It's over.
- We have a long way to go.
- Do we have a long way to go?
- Yes, in my opinion.
- Really?
- It domes over the rim.
(Does it dome over it?)
- Gosh. That was crazy.
- Goodness.
- Now, it's a bit risky.
- Yes. Now, it's risky.
Is it even possible?
- They know it from experience.
- Exactly.
You can tell that it has risen quite a bit.
(The two with the experience have the upper hand.)
Just one drop.
I poured way more than I thought.
I poured more than I meant to.
Is this really possible?
I poured more than I wanted to.
Gosh. You actually did it.
- It's bulging over the rim, right?
- Is it Hyun Bin's... Hold on.
- It's bulging over, right?
- Yes.
It'll be over if the wind blows.
- Goodness.
- Gosh. It bulges over like that.
It'll be over within three tries.
- This is a 2-on-2 match.
- I'm in trouble.
I think so too.
- Jae Seok, let's team up.
- I'm off the hook for sure.
- I'll pass it to them.
- Okay. Go for it.
(A single drop)
(Touching)
(Amazed)
(Touched again)
He's so sly.
(It's a fine skill executed by the experienced one.)
Gosh. You really don't want to pay for lunch.
- Gosh.
- Gosh. It's like a pudding.
It's bulging high above the rim.
- It'll be over soon.
- Yes.
(It's Hyun Bin's turn again.)
It's so difficult.
- It's on them now.
- Yes.
Gosh.
- Hyun Bin.
- Is your neck really stiff?
Hyun Bin is suffering a lot.
(The variety show pros are relaxed.)
- You should go for it.
- What? Come on, Hyun Bin.
- Hyun Bin.
- Here we go.
Relax.
(Safe!)
- It didn't overflow.
- No, it didn't.
You can see the water rising above the rim, right?
He doesn't want to pay for lunch either.
The look on your face is so real.
(Hyun Bin who hates to pay for lunch does exist.)
What's wrong with this cup?
(The inexperienced ones ride the momentum.)
Gosh. Seriously.
- No. They should get the penalty.
- It should've been over.
- What? What's happening?
- Don't move.
What just happened?
Gosh.
(Now, one person becomes really serious.)
Come on. The water is rising way above the rim.
Gosh.
What is this?
It's rising this much above the rim.
- Good job.
- Gosh. Thank you.
One drop.
- It overflowed.
- Okay.
(Jae Seok, it is.)
- What's wrong with the side?
- Why?
(Genuinely happy)
(Today's lunch is on Jae Seok.)
It overspilled.
Do Hwan has come to see me pay.
Gosh. Thank you.
(Polite)
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- It was great.
- Let's get coffee.
- We should get coffee.
- Right? Then we go to...
- Yes. We should get coffee...
before we go.
- What?
- What? Yu Jae Seok?
- What? Really? I love it.
- What? Yes.
- They're so cute.
- Aren't you Woo Do Hwan?
(Confused)
- You're right.
- Seriously. Hey.
- "Aren't you Woo Do Hwan?"
- Uncle Hyun Bin is there too.
- Have you seen him before?
- Where are you heading to?
"Bloodhounds" was fun.
- Thank you.
- We're going to get bossam.
- Really?
- It was good.
- Can we take a photo?
- Can we get a photo?
Sure.
- They're adorable.
- Do we know them?
- Hey.
- What?
Aren't you Yoo Yeon Seok?
- I am.
- You're right.
- "Hospital Playlist" was great.
You watch a lot of dramas.
They're cute.
(Smiling like a dad)
Go ahead and take a photo.
- Can someone take it for us?
- Okay. Sure.
Hyun Bin.
Why are you...
- He's super famous.
- He is...
Is that so?
- Is the background okay?
- He's Hyun Bin.
- It's okay.
- He's in "Made in Korea."
One, two, three.
(Doing his best in the meantime)
Gosh. My legs are shaky.
It went so smoothly as if it were all planned.
(It's a photo taken by none other than Hyun Bin.)
- They're adorable. He's holding...
- Okay.
- his hand so tightly.
- Enjoy your meal. You're handsome.
- Thank you.
- Both of you are good-looking.
- Bye.
- Study hard.
- They're cute.
- Yes, really.
They're very sociable.
The light has changed right away.
- It has changed.
- It's nice.
(They hurry to get coffee after a surprise fan meet.)
Let's see. Non-coffee.
Are you buying these also?
- No, we have to play a game.
- Do we play it again?
I'll buy this one.
- Okay.
- Let them choose the card.
- It's on me.
- Okay.
I'll let you treat me.
Do you want some coffee?
- Thank you. I'll bring them to you.
- Okay. Thank you.
Thanks for the coffee.
(Sitting after placing their orders)
- This basement is nice.
- Yes.
Goodness.
- It's nearby.
- I want to go home...
with peace of mind.
(Tearing up)
When I fail a mission,
it feels like I've ruined...
a really important scene.
(Nodding)
Hey, that's exactly how it feels.
It's an important scene, but it doesn't go as you planned.
But usually, as for those important scenes,
they'll let me do it again if I want to.
- It's an expensive scene, then.
- That's right.
- That's right. It's...
- But...
the director might say,
"It was good."
- Yes, they say that sometimes.
- What do you do?
Do you go along with their opinion?
Or do you ask for a retake?
When I worked with Woo Min Ho, the director of "Made in Korea,"
I redid the take.
But since I knew what part was good...
for him to say "Okay,"
I went for a completely different version.
So that he could choose one when he edits the show.
- So that he could see.
- Yes.
It happened all the time. The director said, "I liked it."
"What do you think, Hyun Bin?" And he'd go, "One more time."
- Even when the director liked it.
- You wanted a different version.
- Yes. I tried it differently.
- He did it again.
- He'd be able to choose later on.
- Yes.
Do you work out every day, Jae Seok?
- Not every day?
- No.
I work out 2 to 3 times a week.
Is there any workout you do other than weightlifting?
I've transferred from the gym I went to a new one...
because I changed to a completely new workout.
- To what?
- It's a mixture of workouts.
It combines HYROX and CrossFit.
- I see.
- You do those together.
- It involves bodyweight exercises.
- Something like that.
He does a lot of action shots.
When you do lots of action shots,
- you have to stay fit, right?
- You have to maintain your body.
Do Hwan does boxing too.
- Boxing is really hard.
- For "Bloodhounds."
- Yes.
- It was tough.
The other actions only require a light touch.
But when we're wearing gloves,
we actually need to punch and get hit.
- It hurts you quite a bit.
- That's right.
- Shall we get going?
- Let's get going.
- It's at 12:40pm.
- Yes.
- No more failures.
- No more.
- We won't fail anymore.
- No.
We have to succeed this time.
It's from Oh Seung Ju.
"Ding-dong. When the bell rings,"
"I start tightening the screws between people and the machine."
"Sitting in a 1m² cubicle,"
"I bring a machine back to life,"
"and I bring a smile back to people's faces."
- "Every day feels meaningful,"
- What?
"but for once, I want to loosen up my own screws and laugh."
- "Loosen the screws?"
- Is it a service center?
Is it a center where they repair the devices?
Let's really do it this time.
- Really.
- Seriously.
How many times are we going to psych ourselves up today?
No more failures.
- It's my birthday, so I'll do it.
- Yes.
(They head to the place while psyching themselves up.)
This is it.
We're here.
- It's a service center, indeed.
- It's a service center.
(They've arrived at an S Electronics Service Center.)
It's over here.
- It's S Electronics.
- Counter 12.
- It feels...
- Good afternoon.
- Welcome.
- Counter 12.
- It's that way.
- He's back there.
- He's over there.
He's here.
Gosh. Hello.
- Are you Seung Ju?
- Yes. Hello.
Gosh. You are...
You are actually working right now.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice. S Electronics Service Center.
Yes.
I handle everything related to phones.
- I repair them.
- I see.
And I solve any problems people have with them.
- Cool.
- I see.
- Nice. That's great.
How long have you worked here?
It's been exactly ten years.
- I see.
- This year.
The products here are made in Korea.
- That's correct.
- That's right.
It's all about "Made in Korea" today.
(In sync)
- That was awesome.
- Hyun Bin loves that.
- These products are made in Korea.
- Yes.
In the summer,
what kind of issues do people have the most?
As you might have guessed,
- after the vacation, - They play in the water.
- water damage is the most common.
- That's right.
That's the most common issue.
What about in winter? Does it vary by season?
Because they handle their phones with the gloves on,
- They drop their phones.
- they slip and fall.
- It hurts so much when you drop it.
- Gosh.
It does happen.
Because we wear gloves in the winter,
- our phones slip.
- Yes.
(Relating to it)
By the way, there are some functions...
only the tech-savvy people know about.
- That's right.
- What are those?
(Are there secret tips on phones?)
It's not a function, but there's a way...
that allows you to use your phone longer...
- by optimizing it.
- What?
- What is it?
- I'm so curious.
As for your phone,
how many times do you turn it off...
- in a week?
- I hardly turn it off.
I don't know about a week,
but I think I turn it off 2 to 3 times a month.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I've never turned it off.
- Because of the temporary memory...
The best way is to reboot it once every other day.
- What?
- Yes. It's best...
to turn it off completely and turn it back on.
- Why?
- It's because...
The temporary memory piles up inside your phone.
It's called cache memory.
When you reboot it, it optimizes it by resetting it.
- These guys need to rest too.
- Yes.
- To get rid of unnecessary stuff.
Do you really turn it off every other day?
As for it, I do it once a week.
I can't turn it off every other day.
Then why did you say so to us?
He told us to turn it off every other day.
- Is it recommended to do so?
- It's recommended.
- For our customers.
- Turn it off at least once a week.
My wife crossed paths with Jae Seok before.
- Really? How so?
- It wasn't a big deal.
Okay.
She used to be a cameraman.
- A cameraman?
- Yes.
- When you were in "Family Outing,"
she did the shooting.
- For "Family Outing."
- Was she the cameraman...
for "Family Outing?"
Yes. I don't know if you'd remember.
Her name is Kwak In Yeong.
- She worked with the seniors...
- Okay.
to shoot their reactions.
I think I remember her.
- That's your wife.
- Yes.
Did she say anything about the shoot today?
She told me not to talk about her.
(But he talked about her so much.)
- You talked about her the longest.
- Right.
Maybe that's why while you're surrounded by cameras,
you speak so well. Probably better than us.
- That's why.
- No.
- I can't look this way.
- Why not?
They're so much more handsome.
I should move this way.
This is better.
Yeon Seok.
- Yeon Seok.
- Why am I lumped in with you?
I happened to sit here.
- Hey, Yeon Seok.
- I'm supposed to be here.
Yeon Seok, come join me.
- I belong to this group.
- Yeon Seok, come here already.
You're leaning quite this way now.
- You're leaning quite this way now.
- Nonsense.
- Hey, Hyun Bin.
- You're now in this group.
This feels right.
Good. For us to go home proudly,
we really need to succeed here.
- Yes. Good.
- Yes.
Let's get started.
(Sighing)
Hyun Bin, why did you sigh?
(Getting stressed already)
Though she's not here in person,
we should get In Yeong a present, right?
- Yes.
- She's my former colleague.
The present for Round One.
"I want to leave a neat and tidy impression on customers."
"Braun electric shaver."
- Nice.
- That one's a good one.
(Braun electric shaver, an essential to leave a neat first impression)
(A surge of interest)
- Nice.
- That's great.
You do have a beard.
I become a bearded man at night.
- You grow hair fast.
- I'm a bearded man.
Good.
(Tweezers Controller)
(Use the repair tweezers...)
(to stack 5 nuts in a relay.)
(Ring the bell within the time limit to complete the mission.)
(Time limit: 30 seconds)
- Gosh.
- It requires precision.
(It gives him a headache already.)
Gosh. This is a tough one.
It requires a delicate touch.
- Do we get 30 seconds again?
- Yes.
Not all games have a 30-second limit, right?
Usually, it's 30 seconds.
Gosh. Here we go again.
We sit for this one.
Okay. Within 30 minutes, each piles 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5 nuts.
Stack on top of that.
- On top of this?
- Yes.
- On top of this nut?
- Sideways.
When it collapses, you can try it again.
His hands are quite shaky.
- No. This is slippery.
- You shouldn't hold the table.
It shouldn't touch.
Is it better not to touch it?
Darn it.
(Darn it.)
- Hold on.
- Darn it.
Gosh. We're in trouble.
No. It's...
- The third one is tough.
- Is that so?
When they touch...
- One...
- Okay.
- Do it like this.
- Like this.
- One, two, three, four, and five.
- I grab it like this.
- Okay.
(Practice)
We can hold it in advance, right?
(They can grab the nut in advance.)
Of course, we can.
- The table is shaky.
- Yes.
Let's not touch the table.
Good.
- That was good.
- It took 20 seconds.
That's good.
It does work.
Open for the second present.
(Feeling more confident)
- Now, let's go for it right away.
- Yes. Sounds good.
- Let's do this.
- Let's do it.
- Let's go.
- In 1, 2, 3,
- let's go.
- Let's go.
Try not to touch the table.
No more failures.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
Ready. Set.
(1st try)
He holds it in a unique way.
- You can do it again. Slowly.
- You can try it again. It's okay.
- Let's not touch the table.
- Gosh.
Place it up there.
Yes.
No, it's collapsing.
Gosh. It collapsed.
Do it again. We don't have time.
Let's hurry and try it again.
- Five, four, - Hurry.
- three, two...
- Here.
(First try failed.)
It's hard to place it.
You have to hold it correctly.
- You have to align them together.
- Okay.
It makes it easier for us to stack them up.
- It should...
- Don't stack them in a zigzag.
(Hyun Bin recommends stacking them in the same direction.)
- Not like that.
- It should face...
That's right.
You can't put it on by hand, Hyun Bin.
Exactly.
- What?
- You put on the nut by hand.
Slowly.
(Using his hands)
- I shouldn't put it on like this.
- No.
I see. I didn't know. We should start over, then.
- Yes.
- We should retry it.
- I didn't know.
- We should start over.
- We shouldn't break the rule.
- It can't be aired, can it?
Should we start over?
Let's go for it. Let's go!
- Let's do it.
- No more failures for us.
Second try. Here we go.
Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
Set.
(2nd try)
We can do it. We just need to be slow.
- Good.
- Slowly.
- I won't be watching.
- Gosh.
- Move sideways.
- That's it.
- Should I make a cross?
- I think it'll be fine.
I think I did it wrong.
- Keep going.
- Let go of it.
- Okay.
- That's it.
We have lots of time, Jae Seok. Take your time.
(They'll succeed if they put one on.)
We have lots of time. Take your time.
- I think it'll work. There you go.
- Yes!
Ring the bell.
Success!
(They did it!)
It's over.
It's over. We did it.
(He won the electric shaver in Round 1.)
- Gosh.
- That was good.
- Nice.
- Yes.
- Gosh. It's hot.
- It's hot.
- Good job.
- Round 1, success!
Nice.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- It was only Round One.
- You were nervous, weren't you?
I can't even breathe.
- Well...
- We pulled it off in two tries.
Choose whether to move on to Round Two or not.
You can say go or stop.
One, two, three.
- Go.
- Indeed.
- We have many tries left.
- Okay.
It's a go, of course.
"Make a difference when taking out a business card."
"A Louis Vuitton cardholder that suits the premium service."
(The Round 2 present: An LV cardholder wallet)
A Louis Vuitton cardholder?
- They give out a luxury brand one.
- Gosh.
(The designer cardholder is here.)
- They give out a luxury brand one.
- Gosh.
(Totally mesmerized)
Do Hwan loves it.
- You're jealous.
- It's interesting.
It's a designer cardholder.
- We have to get it for him.
- What's for Round Two?
(Round 2)
(The number of the nuts...)
(increases to 7.)
- Are we adding two more?
- That's too many.
(7 nuts?)
- Two more?
- Two more.
That's a lot.
That means everyone but 1 will handle 2 nuts.
One, two, three, four, five, six, and seven.
You'll be the last one.
(Feeling lots of pressure)
In that case,
- one, two, three, four, - I think Yeon Seok is good at this.
- five, six, and seven.
- The order should be...
- Let's change the order.
- Yes.
Let's do 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, and 7.
- Okay.
- I'll go there.
Do Hwan will be the last one, right?
- Is this the spot for the last one?
- Yes. Number 7.
- Is this the 7th spot?
- It's 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Then 5, 6, and 7.
The rest of you will each get two nuts.
- I'm in trouble.
- Do Hwan who won't fail anymore.
Also, don't forget to ring the bell.
- Yes. Ring it, Do Hwan.
- Okay.
(Glancing)
Why don't you handle one more since you were good at it?
Come on.
- You can even handle three.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
It went like this.
Try to be...
Look at his pinky. That's being detailed.
(Stacking stably with his pinky as a support)
- Gosh. This isn't easy.
- Gosh.
It isn't easy.
(Everyone is getting better at it.)
Gosh. I'm in trouble.
- My pinky can't touch it. Thanks.
- It doesn't touch.
(Hyun Bin's polite hand)
(Practice, success!)
(Great teamwork by the two)
- Okay.
- Gosh.
Bin supported his pinky.
(Made by Hyun Bin)
- Okay. Let's go for it.
- Gosh.
- It's so hard.
- Let's do this.
In 1, 2, 3,
- let's go.
- Let's go.
He's the husband...
- of my former colleague.
- That's right.
- We have to do this.
- We need to get her a present.
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 3.)
(3rd try)
You can't do it in advance.
We can try it again.
We can do it again.
(3rd try)
- Seriously.
- This is driving me nuts.
What are you doing?
(What a commotion!)
What was that?
(3rd try)
- We have time left?
- Yes.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
Gosh, that was so close!
(They fail with their third try.)
That was so close!
(Heavily congested area)
(Reading the room)
- Come here, Do Hwan.
- Right.
- This is...
- He will just place one?
(The spot where only 1 needs to be placed)
Do Hwan is feeling a lot of stress.
He's feeling a lot of stress.
(It's his second time being in a slump.)
We must not fail anymore.
- We must not fail anymore.
- Right.
All right. Let's do this.
You look nervous as well.
Bin and Do Hwan...
are feeling very nervous.
(Stretching all of a sudden)
Very nervous.
- Should we switch?
- Right.
- You should feel free to switch.
- Use this moment to relax.
- Right.
This really makes you feel nervous.
There's so much tension.
Let's practice.
We'll practice. Go.
(Practice)
Do Hwan.
You're shaking even more.
(They pass the halfway mark.)
- All right.
- That's all we need to do.
There you go.
Gosh, this makes me feel so nervous.
This is good enough.
(They pass the practice round quite easily.)
During the actual round, let's take our hands off the table.
Right.
- Our hands are shaking so much.
- Right.
We did really well just now.
- We're amazing during practice.
- We're amazing.
- We're the best.
- Did you see how cool-headed I was?
- Gosh!
- I was so cool-headed.
- We're cool-headed.
- Right.
- We're cool-headed during practice.
- Nice.
- Let's do it just the same.
- Let's go!
We must say, "Here we go," right?
- Right.
- Can't we signal it like this?
- All right.
- No?
Here we go.
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
(5th try)
It's okay. We still have time.
You go next.
(Fifth try)
Gosh!
Five, four, three, two, one.
(They fail on their fifth try.)
(Feeling troubled)
- Yes?
- Let's change.
- You will go first.
- Right.
How many times did we go?
- That was the 5th try.
- We're on Round 2.
(Frustrated)
But we seem to have a lot more time than expected...
- after giving it a try.
- Right.
Let's finish it in one go slowly.
- We were trying to be too fast.
- Right.
- We kept failing at the start.
- We'll take more time.
- We should... Right.
- Should we take it slow?
- This is our sixth try. Let's go.
- Don't feel nervous.
- Just like during practice.
- All right.
- We can do it again if it falls.
- One, two, three.
- Let's go!
- That sounded like a wise saying.
- "We can do it again if it falls."
- "If it falls."
He said a lot of sayings today.
"We must not fail anymore."
"We can do it again if it falls."
And he's the one who shakes the most.
He makes so many mistakes.
(The wise saying maker shakes a lot.)
- Let's go!
- We can do this.
- These can be put up.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
- Ready.
- Place them at the front.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
This is better, right?
("We can do it again if it falls.")
Set.
(6th try)
- Slowly.
- We have time.
We have time. We can take it slow.
Take it slow from now on.
Take it slow. We just need to do three more.
Take it slow. We have time.
Done. We got this.
(Swaying)
(6th try)
Okay.
(There's just one left until they make it.)
Take it slow. We have time. We have 15 seconds.
- The bell. Done.
- Hit the bell!
- Success!
- Gosh, we did it!
- The bell. Done.
- Hit the bell!
- Success!
- Gosh, we did it!
- Gosh!
- Nice one!
- Nice!
Gosh!
Nice!
- Bin!
- Gosh!
That was great.
Bin, your hands are so sweaty.
- We did it!
- That was so tough!
- Done!
- Nice!
- Now, we have four tries left.
We passed Round Two.
Think carefully if you want to move on to Round Three.
- There's a chance left.
It will get harder,
and the prize will be greater.
But if we fail,
- Everything will be lost.
- everything will be lost.
Did you get the hang of it?
I did.
(You got the hang of it?)
Think carefully about it.
One, two, three.
- Go!
- Gosh.
I will trust Do Hwan.
- He said he got the hang of it.
- Gosh.
Let's check the prize for Round Three.
We have four tries.
- The chance can be used as well.
- Right.
"Leveling up for a healthier back while working or gaming."
"The Hermes of chairs, Herman Miller chair."
Herman Miller?
That's the best chair...
- that can be used in an office.
- Awesome!
- It's here!
- It's here! The chair is here.
It's right there.
Isn't that the best chair that can be used in an office?
(Highest tier of office chairs, Herman Miller chair)
(Round 3: Success if 1 person stacks 4 nuts each)
(Time limit of 50 seconds)
- We do get 50 seconds.
- Four each.
Here? In front of each of us?
We must each stack our own pile.
Must we do it in order?
Four like this?
- This is doable.
- I think we got this.
All right. Let's practice.
Ready.
- Hold on.
- It's one person at a time, right?
Start. Do Hwan will go first.
(Practice)
- It's one person at a time?
- After one pile,
- the next person goes.
- We get 50 seconds in total?
- The last one will have no time.
- We get 50 seconds.
Right.
Take it slow. It's okay.
Nice.
- It's okay.
- You used 17 seconds.
What?
On his own?
I used 17 seconds?
(He used 17 seconds in a flash.)
My turn won't come.
How many seconds were used now?
Around 35 seconds.
(Around 35 seconds were used even before half of them.)
- This is bad. We're short on time.
- This is going to be tough.
- Should I stack two at once?
- There's not enough time.
We have 50 seconds?
Let's try to get it done first.
Gosh, we have to pass Round Three.
We must pass today.
Okay.
- Did you get the hang of it?
- I got the hang of it.
- He got it.
- I'll go first.
- Right.
It's better to get it done quickly, isn't it?
- Yes.
- Come here.
- I have to go there?
- Right.
- Okay. I'll go first.
All four piles must stand before the bell is rung.
It can't fall over.
Okay. I got the hang of it.
- I got it.
- It should be straight.
I can get it done quickly now.
Should we give it a try?
- Can we give it a try, Do Hwan?
- Sure.
- All right.
- I got the hang of it too.
- I can do it quickly now.
- Okay.
Done. Let's go for Round Three.
- Let's go.
- We have four tries left.
The chance can be used.
- Here we go.
- Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 7.)
This is doable.
("I think we got this.")
You must keep it down before you start.
Hold on.
Come on.
He got himself ready.
- The rules must be followed.
- Right.
Ready. Set.
(7th try)
- Take it slow.
- Right.
(7th try)
It's okay.
Take it slow.
We still have time.
- We still have time.
- There are ten seconds left.
Ten seconds.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
(They fail with their seventh try.)
Wait! What?
(The nuts are strung together?)
Is that allowed?
(That is allowed.)
I think this can become a good method.
Wait. That might work. Hold on.
They're all strung together?
String 3 of them together and pile them up 1 by 1?
They have to be pulled out slightly.
- Really?
- No.
I think it's okay.
(The nut tower gets built in a flash.)
This is the best method.
Hey! This is a good method.
It's nice, isn't it? It's working for me.
It's quick.
I think I can get it done within 11 seconds.
(Bin tries the new method as well.)
I can do it.
I'm serious.
Your hands tend to shake during the actual round.
Gosh!
I hate saying, "Here we go."
I'll go first.
- I hate that so much.
- I'll say it.
"Here we go!"
- I'll say, "Here we go."
- Okay.
Gosh, it's been a while since I've seen Bin get mad.
It's been a while since I've seen him get mad.
(He moves to a different spot to avoid saying, "Here we go.")
- All right. Okay.
- All right.
I'll really get it done in five seconds.
- I did it!
- I'm confident.
- I got it. We have three tries.
- I got it.
Do Hwan's method is amazing.
We have to give this to Director In Young.
(Will they be able to pass Round 3?)
- Let's go!
- Here we go!
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 8.)
(8th try)
(He gets it done in 10 seconds.)
We have time.
Gosh!
You did it! You just need to pull it out.
(He just needs to pull it out.)
Gosh! You did it!
You just need to pull it out.
- You just need to pull it out.
- Quiet!
(Bin makes it.)
There are ten seconds left!
Ten seconds?
(8th try)
Five, four, three, two...
(They fail with their eighth try.)
He did this!
"Quiet!"
(Bin used around 30 seconds on his own.)
This makes me become spineless.
All I can think of is that I feel relieved it wasn't me.
- But...
- Do Hwan.
- Well...
Will you use it?
It didn't even take three seconds just now.
He gets nervous during the actual round.
It didn't even take three seconds.
- He's another Practice Messi.
- It's really tough, isn't it?
Did you see that?
He's so good at it.
The chance should be used. There are only two tries left.
- Will you use the chance?
- Yes. I will.
It must be used.
You'll draw a chance.
- There are five of them.
- Right.
- There's also a bad one.
- We're so good during practice.
- All right.
Why can't we do it?
(He uses the chance before the 9th try.)
Please be a good one. Reduce the number of nuts.
- Please read it for us.
- It won't even take three seconds.
"For this try, there will be more time given."
(Lucky: For this try, there will be more time given.)
You will be given ten more seconds.
- We'll get 60 seconds?
- That's nice.
- That's a good one.
- Nice!
- Nice.
- Okay.
- Ten seconds will be enough...
even if one person struggles, right?
- Then...
- Are you talking about Bin?
- Do you want to go first?
- No. I'm talking about myself.
- Sounds good.
(Do Hwan goes 1st as he feels comfortable with it.)
All right.
- Let's go!
- This is an opportunity.
It's an opportunity, Do Hwan.
Do Hwan!
Please!
You can do it again if it falls as you're first.
Really?
(They practice first.)
Gosh, I can get it done with my eyes closed during practice.
It's easy during practice.
- Let's go for it.
- Right.
(He does it easily.)
- It's easy during practice, right?
- Gosh, I feel so mad.
Gosh!
This is a true chance.
- We got this!
- This is a chance.
- Let's do this.
- We have to do this.
Let's think of this as our last chance.
All right.
- Let's go.
- We must not fail anymore.
- One, two, three. Let's go!
- Let's go!
Let's give out presents...
- on my birthday.
- Here we go!
- Right.
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
(Ninth try with ten more seconds with the chance)
It's okay.
You can do this.
Right.
We have time.
We have a lot of time.
- There we go.
(Letting out a breath)
- It might fall.
- It mustn't fall!
We have a lot of time.
- It might fall.
- We have a lot of time.
I think we've done it.
I think we got this.
- There are ten seconds left.
- It's okay, Yeon Seok.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
(He managed to stack the nuts.)
The bell!
Two, one.
- One.
- The bell!
- We did it!
- It didn't matter who ran the bell!
- That was never mentioned!
- Hey!
- Time out.
- Gosh!
- But...
- The one to ring the bell...
- was never mentioned.
- That was never mentioned.
Was that part of the rules?
You pass after each person stacks four nuts...
and the bell gets rung.
We have to take turns, right?
- Right.
- And ring the bell?
(There wasn't a rule on who had to ring the bell!)
- The last person...
- Success!
Success!
(Bin focused until the very end.)
- Finally!
- Gosh!
(Overwhelmed)
Awesome!
Round Three, success!
Two, one.
(Bin covered Yeon Seok with just 1 second left.)
(Yeon Seok's savior)
- Gosh!
- I forgot!
- You should've rung the bell!
- I forgot.
I was thinking, "Let's not make a mistake."
- Gosh!
- "There's enough time."
My hands were shaking like crazy.
My gosh.
- Congratulations!
- It was a relief...
- you managed to hit it instead.
- Exactly.
- Bin hit it instead.
- Right.
As a result, we can give him all of the presents!
(He wins the razor, designer wallet, and high-end chair.)
Gosh, congratulations!
- Gosh!
- We still managed to do it once.
We can give Director In Young the presents.
You can give out presents on your birthday.
- Right. If we failed to do so, - Right.
it would've made me feel really uncomfortable.
I was going to come again next week.
- Exactly.
- What a neat finish.
We would like to thank everyone that was on the show.
- Thank you!
Thank you!
- Gosh, what a relief!
- Congratulations!
Gosh, what a relief!